That person...
She's crying?
Are you okay?
Summer break ends too quickly.
What should I do? I haven't even finished my homework yet.
Me neither.
There is someone, right? Someone you like.
The one Akihime likes... is Kisaragi-sensei?
For what reason... am I hiding?
Good morning, Tsuwabuki-sama.
Oh, hello.
Oh, right. May I have a bit of your time?
Yes?
Miss.
I have brought Tsuwabuki-sama.
Matsuda, you may go now.
Yes, Miss.
Umm, what?
About that incident... You didn't tell anyone, right?
Eh? What incident?
The incident at camp!
At camp? Oh, you mean when I carried you during the courage...
Not so loud!
I won't tell anyone, I promise.
And this conversation too. Don't tell anyone.
Matsuda, let's go.
Yes, Miss.
Excuse us.
No matter who Akihime likes, it's none of my business.
Though that's what I thought...
Then why...
Sumomo, don't push yourself too much.
It's good to rest when you need to.
Nako-chan...
What happened?
Yaeno-san.
Sorry, the shop wasn't open today and I came to help, but...
Did something happen?
N-Nothing's wrong. But thank you.
Haru!
There was nothing to do, so...
While bringing food I came to help on something.
You know that you can eat sunflower seeds, right?
Since it should taste better than the ones we sell, I thought of trying one.
Eh? Was it okay?
Actually, it tasted horrible. It was really bitter.
Noboku-san told me this:
"That T-shirt doesn't suit you."
"If it were summer, it would suit you better."
So I said this:
It's okay for someone who is weak and without muscles to wear it in summer, right?
Akihime-san, what do you think?
If I could talk like that, I would…
Tsuwabuki, that's not a weed.
Eh? Ah, sorry.
I... think I should go home for today.
Right! When I'm Yuki-chan, I can talk more about certain things.
I’m so pitiful...
Welcome, Yuki-chan.
This is... an acorn?
It was on the ground at the greenhouse.
It was all alone stuck on the ground, so...
It looked like a stray.
A stray? Sumomo thinks of interesting things.
Normally, looking at an acorn you wouldn't think of it like that.
Sumomo, did something happen?
Ore, err... I'll listen to you if there's anything you want to tell me. You might even feel refreshed after doing so.
Thank you Yuki-chan, you're so kind.
When I saw this, I remembered...
During the entrance ceremony a year ago in spring...
In the cherry blossom forest behind the school,
I got lost.
I had gotten separated from Nako-chan.
You had gotten lost during... the entrance ceremony?
Could it be...?
I... was nervous and scared.
I was about to cry.
But then...
I met this boy...
The girl from back then was... Sumomo?
He was also a new student, and he even took me all the way back to the entrance ceremony.
I was… very happy.
Sumomo, about that person, do you...
Yes.
But, it may be that my first love won't come true.
Because that person already has someone that they like...
Sumomo!
The ring!
What?!
This place was a waterway for children. Earlier...
Because the star drop went in, it became like this?
The star drop!
Sumomo, are you okay?
I'll give it a try...
Ruche Puria...
Still weak against water, I see.
And you still call yourself a Stellar Spinear?
Aspalas-san?
Prima Aspalas!
Say it right!
Whatever. In order to see who the superior Stellar Spinear is, this a battle.
But… A battle?
Enough talk!
Beam Cometi Aqua!
Ara Deum Mei!
Sumomo?
I'll try my very best!
Beam Cometi Aqua!
Somehow you made it.
It’s a full on fair and square battle!
Sumomo! Sumomo!!!
Sumomo!
Got it!
It's fast!
Miss please be careful, that star drop is no push over.
Just as I expected.
It should be this difficult for it to be worthwhile.
Sumomo, are you okay?
If I make a mistake, I quickly cry.
But Yuki-chan is with me so I’ll try my best.
Sumomo, it’s a new Recipe!
Moterios Oludin Radium!
Miss!
Puruvi Radius!
Spectacular! Miss is the complete victor!
Uh, Miss?
What was that… that previous technique?
The Recipe that even I, the best in Saint Aspalas, don’t know…
How can this girl…
P-Please wait Miss! Miss!
Sumomo! Sumomo, are you okay?
Yuki-chan, I’m sorry.
After all that, the star drop... I lost it.
E-Everybody fails from time to time.
You just need to try harder again next time.
I can’t even keep the promise I made with Yuki-chan.
I’m sorry.
Sumomo...
And so, Akihime is really depressed...
Undoubtedly, losing the battle last night was disheartening.
You don’t get it, do you?
Listen carefully. The power of a Stellar Spinear's spell...
The magic’s power reflects the power of the user’s heart.
Their heart?
If something good happens and her heart is happy, then her power increases.
On the other hand, if something sad happens or depression sets in, their power begins to decrease.
Something sad?
Tsuwabuki-kun, is there anything you know?
Who knows…
You don’t know, even though you guys are always together?
E-Even if you say that…
In these situations, I believe that girls will cheer up if they get attention from the person they like.
He took me all the way back to the entrance ceremony.
I was… very happy.
Even if... Akihime really likes me...
As of right now, I can't do anything for her.
It’ll always be troublesome for Akihime.
I can't say anything about what I heard yesterday.
And even more so to smile.
Here.
Have some.
I got the yakisoba bread.
No thanks.
Why? It’s your favorite.
I don’t have any appetite.
Maybe Tsuwabuki-kun is in love or something.
In love?! W-What?!
I'm right, am I not?
Seriously?! Haru in love?
Lies! It can't be!
I mean, it's possible, yes.
But... I'm not really sure...
It may be that staying as friends is what she wants.
That girl, what's she like?
What she's like...
She cries easily.
She's small and insecure.
But, she always tries her best.
She tries hard, and she's very kind-hearted.
I can believe that. There's no mistake about it.
So it's something like this, right?
Tsuwabuki-kun is thinking, "I cannot do anything for that girl," or...
"Even if I confess it would only cause trouble."
Something like that, right?
But you know, Haru...
Those things aren't important to girls.
Keisuke-kun, did something happen with Nobuko?
W-Well, this really isn't about Nobuko-san.
But, as he said...
The important thing is to be honest with your feelings, right?
A confession!
Right! I should tag along and...
Let's just observe quietly.
No, no. I'm worried about Haru confessing properly.
I’m telling you not to interfere. Got it?
Y-Yes…
I have no confidence even though I'm running fast.
But...  But...
Even so...
I...
Aki-
If I...  If I don’t say anything...
But, what...?
Tsuwabuki-kun, what’s wrong?
Well, I...
That is... I was thinking about that flower I was arranging.
Me too.
I couldn't take care of this place a lot.
I wanted to do something for it.
I’ll help.
Not good. It’s almost time.
T-Tsuwabuki-kun... Umm, come this way...
Could you please come with me?
Try standing here.
Akihime, what…
This is…
During the sunset...
For a short while...
It shines likes this.
Amazing.
It’s very beautiful.
U-Umm...
Can we keep this as a secret, just between you and me?
Only us? Does Yaeno not know?
That's right.
I kept it a secret from everyone, even Nako.
For me, when I’m depressed I come here and watch this.
It cheers me up a little.
Tsuwabuki-kun, you looked like you didn’t have any energy.
So I thought that if you saw this, you might cheer up a bit.
Akihime.
Even though you went through all that…
For me... you...
Akihime.
I’m sorry.
The reason why I came here...
And how worried I was about the flowers was a lie.
R-Really?
I was actually looking for you... Akihime.
I...
I… like you, Akihime.
Sumomo-chan’s father is a well-known author.
And her mother?
That is a mystery.
She's in another country right?
I see.
Rumor has it that she's very beautiful.
Just like a goddess.
I want a date with her.
Think of the age difference!